[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 24]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
“Unsoiled Starlight” ]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
[Notice]
Hi,
excuse me.
Could I ask if the security guard colleague
working here
during the renovation is around?
Colleague?
What colleague?
I've always been the only one here.
He has slightly dark skin
and a mole under his right eyebrow.
You must be mistaken.
There was no one like that
on our security team.
Did you set up
a temporary counter outside?
No.
This is the only place open to the public.
The rest are internal offices.
So,
from the very beginning,
the security guards
at the Intellectual Property Center,
the staff,
and the documents
were all fake.
Someone set a trap for me,
leaving me nowhere to escape.
They were just
waiting for me to walk right into it.
Who hates me this much,
and would go to such lengths
just to bring about my downfall?
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Even if Lisen holds you accountable
for the two million loss,
I will cover it for you.
Zhuo Yu'an,
are you going to fix things
for me every time from now on?
This is my own mistake,
and I want to take responsibility for it.
Do you have to draw
such a clear line with me?
I just don't want to hide behind others
and be a coward.
Hi, Mom.
Where are you?
I'm dealing with something outside.
What's wrong?
Come back quickly.
About your marriage,
we all know.
Long time no see, Tinglan.
Why are you everywhere?
I'm here for work.
What about you?
Looks like you've had a rough time
while I was away.
Those dark circles under your eyes
are pretty bad.
Do you have to keep staring at me
like that?
Your hair's a mess.
It's in the way.
Good luck.
Tinglan.
The patent author is suing.
You won't win this case,
so just pay up.
Mr. Gao.
Lawyer Xiao,
Take a look.
It's impossible to win this.
But this is our last chance.
Lawyer Xiao.
Just let me try.
Tell me,
how should you
solve this?
Divorce.
Come on.
Impossible.
Do you know who she is?
She is my wife.
Besides you two,
she is the closest person to me.
What a joke.
This woman...
can never marry into
the Zhuo family anyway.
Why?
Because she is Shu Minghai's daughter.
Shu-Shu Minghai?
Your former subordinate, Shu Minghai?
Who else could it be?
Mom,
what happened before?
Yu'an,
I can't help you this time.
This person
has been the biggest worry
for your father and me all these years.
He was
just an ordinary employee
in your dad's company at the time.
Relying on
your dad's appreciation and promotion,
he made his way up to manager.
Mr. Zhuo,
thank you for trusting me
and giving me such a big project.
Minghai.
Remember
to be rational.
Okay.
I will definitely keep it in mind.
Mr. Zhuo.
We understand
that you value talented people.
But when you place so much in an outsider,
trusting him in every way,
Where dose that
leave us old-timers?
Survival of the fittest
is the basic rule of Zhuo Group
and the law of capital operation.
If you feel a sense of crisis,
you should talk less and do more.
He got to know all kinds of dignitaries
through your dad.
Gradually,
as his wings grew full,
he was no longer willing
to be subordinate to others.
It wasn't long before
he started his own company.
[EPC Project of Intelligence]
[Open auction]
At this public bidding event,
congratulations
to Mr. Shu on winning the bid.
Congratulations!
Survival of the fittest.
You deserve it.
[EPC Project of Intelligence]
[Open Bidding]
He also took various projects
from the group.
But he
only knows how to work
but is not good at
operation and management.
Soon,
the company fell apart
and was on the verge of bankruptcy.
He came to your dad again.
Mr. Zhuo,
My company is a little short
on cash right now.
We urgently need
a guarantee deposit for a project.
Could you help me out?
Okay.
Thank you.
Your dad was only tring to
help him out.
But who would've thought
he was really looking to
have your father share the risk?
In the end,
the company still went bankrupt,
leaving over 100 million yuan in debt.
And then he fled.
Zhuo Group
had to take on all the debt.
This caused quite a stir
among the board members.
Your father was
under a lot of pressure.
It took him years to pay off the debt.
After that,
he never trusted outsiders again.
What's wrong?
I went to see my parents.
Did they give you a hard time?
No.
Zhuo Yu'an.
Thank you.
Can you change "thank you"
to another three words?
I love you.
Shu Tinglan.
Yeah?
Between us,
we don't need to draw such clear lines.
I want to face many things
together with you.
Don't leave me.
This is why I asked you to leave her.
But Dad,
Shu Tinglan is innocent.
I don't think so.
Shu Minghai was heavily in debt
and had bad conduct.
He kept another woman on the side
and even had a child with her.
A child growing up in such an environment,
no matter how good-natured she may be,
will be influenced by it.
Dad,
You haven't even met her.
How can you tell if she's good or bad?
Yu'an,
after so many years of hard work,
our group has built
a precise and efficient operating system
that is stable and secure.
And you will
inherit the group in the future.
If you marry the daughter of a traitor
who harmed the group's interests,
how can I explain to
the board of directors
and the group members?
Alright, don't be mad.
Don't be mad.
It's getting cold.
I told you to dress warmer.
Let's go.
Go back and get some rest.
Yu'an.
The reason you've grown into
who you are today,
with such
an optimistic and resilient character,
is that your mother and I
have carefully nurtured you
all these years.
I'm old now.
I absolutely won't allow
any more accidents to happen.
Mr. Zhuo.
Calling this late at night?
Your wife won't get jealous?
Wen Jian,
let's meet.
Sure.
I'd love to see you too.